playcombo.com 2019-08-20

# Privacy Policy - Free games online - Playcombo.com

Privacy Policy Playcombo Games ("Playcombo") is committed to ensuring our websites (www.playcombo.com; www.playcombo.*; www.*.playcombo.*) and any published apps (under the publisher name: Playcombo or Playcombo Games) are fun and safe environments. Playcombo does not actively run a user registration system, forum, chat or instant messaging function and thereby does not directly collect any personally identifiable information about our users unless they directly contact us or respond to a feedback survey and provide such information.

Some games featured or hosted on Playcombo that are managed by third-party publishers may contain features such as user registration systems, forums, chat rooms and so forth; which are not managed by Playcombo and are dictated by the privacy policy of the game's publisher.

Playcombo does however collect some basic browsing related data for advertising and analytics purposes. Please consult the below privacy policy which contains further details:

**Cookies and data collected:**

Playcombo collects information about the way visitors and players are using our website through the use of Google Analytics and its related cookie(s). The goal of collecting this data is to make better informed decisions about what games our users are more likely to enjoy and to help improve the experience on Playcombo. The type of information that Google Analytics collects includes browser and operating system type, country, pages visited, time spent on site, date/time stamp and broad demographic information. Google Analytics does not collect any personally identifiable information about you on Playcombo.

Certain games on Playcombo will create "Local shared objects" which allow the game to save game progress so that when you return you can pick up from where you left off. Any game save data is stored only on your computer and not transferred to Playcombo or any other third party. Some games from third-party publishers that are included on Playcombo may offer the ability to save game-progress in the cloud via third-party servers, in which the storage and retrieval of such data is dictated by the privacy policy of such game publisher offering the service.

**External Links:**

Playcombo may link to other web sites and is not responsible for the content or privacy policies of these external sites. Some games on Playcombo also contain links to external sites or may contain requests for personal information for gameplay purposes (e.g. account registration or chatroom features) which are governed by their own individual privacy policies. All users should therefore also be aware of the individual privacy policies within any game that requests personal information such as name or email address. 

**Advertising:**

Playcombo is a free to use website and generates revenue through third-party advertising on the website. Without the support of this advertising Playcombo would not be able to provide new games. These third-party advertising companies may collect and use information about your visits to this and other websites to help determine which advertisements are most suited to your interests and measure performance of any advertising campaigns. In order to collect this information, the third-party may use a cookie or other such as javascript codes. Playcombo has no influence over the policies of third-party advertising networks (except our ability to discontinue using their services). 

If you would like more information about advertising practices and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, you can visit Google's Advertising and Privacy page: <http://www.google.com.au/policies/technologies/ads/>

**Children under 13:**

We are committed to complying with the children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). Playcombo has no user forums or instant message capabilities, and thus no private information pertaining to children can be shared on Playcombo. However certain games hosted on Playcombo may have such features as described in the External Links section, and are governed by their own individual privacy policy. If you have any concern that information related to the privacy of children has been submitted to Playcombo, please contact us at [contact@playcombo.com](mailto:contact@playcombo.com)

**Help and Support:**

Playcombo provides a support email address (contact@playcombo.com) where users may share comments, thoughts, business opportunities or request support with any technical difficulties. From time to time, Playcombo also allows users to provide feedback or answer survey questions to help improve the quality of the website. Any information (including name or email address) that is submitted to Playcombo via any means of communication will never be shared with a third party and will only be used to help answer any questions or troubleshoot any problems that are raised directly in the communication. Email addresses, phone numbers, addresses and other personal information will never be used by Playcombo for marketing purposes such as mailing lists. We want all users of Playcombo to feel comfortable in communicating or providing feedback to us with no fear that their information will used for any other purpose. 

For more information on Google Analytics please see their complete privacy policy:

<http://www.google.com.au/policies/privacy/>

**Updates to this Privacy Policy:**

This Privacy Policy may be changed or modified from time to time. If our information practices change 

This Privacy Policy may be changed or modified from time to time. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to this page to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back to our Privacy Policy periodically. 

**Contact us:**

By using this site, you accept the Playcombo Online Privacy Policy. If you have any concerns please contact us at [ contact@playcombo.com](mailto:contact@playcombo.com). We hope you continue to enjoy your experience on Playcombo.
